[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these actors was not considered for the part of Brom the warrior in the movie Eragon?", "correct_answer": "Sean Connery", "incorrect_answers": ["Jeremy Irons", "Ian McKellan", "Patrick Stewart"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Journey to the Center of the Earth, the person who leads the expedition to the Earths core is honoured with what?", "correct_answer": "Knighthood", "incorrect_answers": ["Honorary degree", "Painting", "Visit from the Queen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What female musician released the single Red Blooded Woman in 2004?", "correct_answer": "Kylie Minogue", "incorrect_answers": ["Beyonce Knowles", "Britney Spears", "Christina Aguilera"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A polar bear is used as the marketing icon for which of these popular products?", "correct_answer": "Klondike Bars", "incorrect_answers": ["Maytag Freezers", "Hoods Ice Cream", "Popsicles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What scientists study recent or fossilized skeletal remains in order to find traces of ancient diseases?", "correct_answer": "Paleopathologists", "incorrect_answers": ["Mycologists", "Parapsychologists", "Epidemiologists"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which year and in which city did the events the movie Miracle was based on took place?", "correct_answer": "1980 - Lake Placid, U.S.A", "incorrect_answers": ["1976 - Innsbruck, Austria", "1984 - Sarajevo, Yugoslavia", "1972 - Sapporo, Japan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is there a cure for the plague?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the temperature of the core of the sun?", "correct_answer": "15,000,000 degrees Celsius", "incorrect_answers": ["70 degrees Celsius", "15,000,000 degrees Fahrenheit", "1,000 degrees Kelvin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the cat detective in the Carole Nelson Douglas series set in Las Vegas?", "correct_answer": "Midnight Louie", "incorrect_answers": ["Lucky Louie", "Tom Thumb", "Mr. Letemride"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "I am suffering from poliosis. What is my problem?", "correct_answer": "Graying of the hair", "incorrect_answers": ["Falling of the teeth", "Shortening due to cartilage deterioration", "Slowing of ones life due to age"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Thomas Lennon starred on the MTV comedy show The State. What year was that show first aired?", "correct_answer": "1993", "incorrect_answers": ["1997", "1994", "2000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Ghost, Sam was killed because his key card (password) was needed to obtain a certain dollar amount from the banking computer.  How much money was it?", "correct_answer": "$4 million", "incorrect_answers": ["$3 million", "$1 million", "$500,000"]}]